[{"answer1":"Humanity","answer2":"Health","answer3":"Honour","answer4":"Household","correctAnswer":2,"id":1,"question":"In the UK, the abbreviation NHS stands for National what Service?"},{"answer1":"Pocahontas","answer2":"Sleeping Beauty","answer3":"Cinderella","answer4":"Elsa","correctAnswer":3,"id":2,"question":"Which Disney character famously leaves a glass slipper behind at a royal ball?"},{"answer1":"Hangar","answer2":"Terminal","answer3":"Concourse","answer4":"Carousel","correctAnswer":4,"id":3,"question":"What name is given to the revolving belt machinery in an airport that delivers checked luggage from the plane to baggage reclaim?"},{"answer1":"Phillips","answer2":"Flymo","answer3":"Chubb","answer4":"Ronseal","correctAnswer":3,"id":4,"question":"Which of these brands was chiefly associated with the manufacture of household locks?"},{"answer1":"Republicanism","answer2":"Communism","answer3":"Conservatism","answer4":" Liberalism","correctAnswer":2,"id":5,"question":"The hammer and sickle is one of the most recognisable symbols of which political ideology?"},{"answer1":"Bratz Dolls","answer2":"Sylvanian Families","answer3":"Hatchimals","answer4":"Transformers","correctAnswer":4,"id":6,"question":"Which toys have been marketed with the phrase “robots in disguise”?"},{"answer1":"Angry","answer2":"Chatty","answer3":"Beautiful","answer4":"Shy","correctAnswer":2,"id":7,"question":"What does the word loquacious mean?"},{"answer1":"Childbirth","answer2":"Broken bones","answer3":"Heart conditions","answer4":"Old age","correctAnswer":1,"id":8,"question":"Obstetrics is a branch of medicine particularly concerned with what?"},{"answer1":"Bow-tie, braces and tweed jacket","answer2":"Wide-brimmed hat and extra long scarf","answer3":"Pinstripe suit and trainers","answer4":"Cape, velvet jacket and frilly shirt","correctAnswer":2,"id":9,"question":"In Doctor Who, what was the signature look of the fourth Doctor, as portrayed by Tom Baker?"},{"answer1":"Ramadan","answer2":"Diwali","answer3":"Lent","answer4":"Hanukkah","correctAnswer":2,"id":10,"question":"Which of these religious observances lasts for the shortest period of time during the calendar year?"},{"answer1":"Bahamas","answer2":"US Virgin Islands","answer3":"Turks and Caicos Islands","answer4":"Bahamas","correctAnswer":1,"id":11,"question":"At the closest point, which island group is only 50 miles south-east of the coast of Florida?"},{"answer1":"Empire State Building","answer2":"Royal Albert Hall","answer3":"Eiffel Tower","answer4":"Big Ben Clock Tower","correctAnswer":4,"id":12,"question":"Construction of which of these famous landmarks was completed first?"},{"answer1":"Gray whale","answer2":"Minke whale","answer3":"Sperm whale","answer4":"Humpback whale","correctAnswer":3,"id":13,"question":"Which of these cetaceans is classified as a “toothed whale”?\n"},{"answer1":"David Lloyd George","answer2":"Harold Wilson","answer3":"James Callaghan","answer4":"John Major","correctAnswer":3,"id":14,"question":"Who is the only British politician to have held all four “Great Offices of State” at some point during their career?"},{"answer1":"Calico Jack","answer2":"Blackbeard","answer3":"Bartholomew Roberts","answer4":"Captain Kidd","correctAnswer":2,"id":15,"question":"In 1718, which pirate died in battle off the coast of what is now North Carolina?"}]